const dataSetEnglish = 
[
    {
        "question": "I spoke to ___________.",
        "Options": ["she", "her"],
        "Answer": "her",
        "Difficulty_Level": "1",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128001"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "Where ___________ you come from?",
        "Options": ["do", "are"],
        "Answer": "do",
        "Difficulty_Level": "1",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128002"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "What time does she ___________ up?",
        "Options": ["get", "gets"],
        "Answer": "get",
        "Difficulty_Level": "1",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128003"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "Where ___________ he live?",
        "Options": ["do", "does"],
        "Answer": "does",
        "Difficulty_Level": "1",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128004"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "I am not ___________ this film.",
        "Options": ["liking", "enjoying"],
        "Answer": "enjoying",
        "Difficulty_Level": "1",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128005"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "I am seeing her ___________ three o'clock.",
        "Options": ["in", "at", "on"],
        "Answer": "at",
        "Difficulty_Level": "1",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128006"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "Easter is ___________ March this year.",
        "Options": ["in", "at", "on"],
        "Answer": "in",
        "Difficulty_Level": "1",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128007"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "She's ___________ work all day today.",
        "Options": ["at", "on"],
        "Answer": "at",
        "Difficulty_Level": "1",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128008"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "I go ___________ by bus.",
        "Options": ["home", "to home"],
        "Answer": "home",
        "Difficulty_Level": "1",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128009"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "It's the second road ___________ the left.",
        "Options": ["in", "at", "on"],
        "Answer": "on",
        "Difficulty_Level": "1",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128010"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "He's arriving ___________ the station at six.",
        "Options": ["at", "on", 'to'],
        "Answer": "at",
        "Difficulty_Level": "1",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128011"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "I ___________ what she's saying.",
        "Options": ["can't understand", "am not understanding"],
        "Answer": "can't understand",
        "Difficulty_Level": "1",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128012"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "I'm going ___________ the bank to get some cash.",
        "Options": ["at", "to"],
        "Answer": "to",
        "Difficulty_Level": "1",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128013"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "The bus stopped ___________ the traffic lights.",
        "Options": ["in", "on", "at"],
        "Answer": "at",
        "Difficulty_Level": "1",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128014"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "She ___________ English twice a week.",
        "Options": ["study",
            "studys",
            "studeis",
            "studies"],
        "Answer": "studies",
        "Difficulty_Level": "1",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128015"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "He didn't work ___________.",
        "Options": ["enough hard", "hard enough"],
        "Answer": "hard enough",
        "Difficulty_Level": "1",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128016"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "There are too ___________ questions in this test.",
        "Options": ["much", "many"],
        "Answer": "many",
        "Difficulty_Level": "1",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128017"
        }
    },



    {
        "question": "She did it ___________ her own.",
        "Options": ["by", "on"],
        "Answer": "on",
        "Difficulty_Level": "2",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128018"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "It is not ___________ mine.",
        "Options": [
            "same as",
            "same like",
            "the same as",
            "the same like",
        ],
        "Answer": "the same as",
        "Difficulty_Level": "2",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128019"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "I didn't see ___________ people there.",
        "Options": ["many", "many of"],
        "Answer": "many",
        "Difficulty_Level": "2",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128020"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "What ___________ you like for dinner tonight?",
        "Options": ["do", "would"],
        "Answer": "would",
        "Difficulty_Level": "2",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128021"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "She did it ___________ Tuesday.",
        "Options": ["last", "on last"],
        "Answer": "last",
        "Difficulty_Level": "2",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128022"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "If I ___________ you, I'd tell her immediately.",
        "Options": ["was", "were", "Either could be used here."],
        "Answer": "Either could be used here.",
        "Difficulty_Level": "2",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128023"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "The radio was ___________ from my car last week.",
        "Options": ["robbed", "stolen"],
        "Answer": "stolen",
        "Difficulty_Level": "2",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128024"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "The person ___________ interviewed me was very friendly.",
        "Options": ["who", "which"],
        "Answer": "who",
        "Difficulty_Level": "2",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128025"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "___________ not the way to do it.",
        "Options": ["That's", "There's", "Either could be used here."],
        "Answer": "That's",
        "Difficulty_Level": "2",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128026"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "I was certain ___________ she would be there.",
        "Options": ["of", "that", "whether"],
        "Answer": "that",
        "Difficulty_Level": "2",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128027"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "If I go, I ___________ speak to her.",
        "Options": ["will", "would"],
        "Answer": "will",
        "Difficulty_Level": "2",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128028"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "If I went, I ___________ speak to her.",
        "Options": ["will", "would"],
        "Answer": "would",
        "Difficulty_Level": "2",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128029"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "That was rude- you ___________ have done it.",
        "Options": ["mustn't", "shouldn't"],
        "Answer": "shouldn't",
        "Difficulty_Level": "2",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128030"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "She found it easy ___________ the test.",
        "Options": ["finish", "to finish", "finishing"],
        "Answer": "to finish",
        "Difficulty_Level": "2",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128031"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the correct spelling?",
        "Options": [
            "necesary",
            "neccesary",
            "necessary",
            "neccessary    ",
        ],
        "Answer": "necessary",
        "Difficulty_Level": "2",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128032"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "Vegetables are good ___________ you.",
        "Options": ["to", "at", "in", "for"],
        "Answer": "for",
        "Difficulty_Level": "2",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128033"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "She spoke ___________ him yesterday.",
        "Options": ["Either could be used here.", "with", "to"],
        "Answer": "Either could be used here.",
        "Difficulty_Level": "2",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128034"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "If I'd been there, I _____ that.",
        "Options": ["wouldn't do", "wouldn't have done", "Either could be used here"],
        "Answer": "wouldn't have done",
        "Difficulty_Level": "2",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128035"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "It was ___________ hot that we couldn't concentrate.",
        "Options": ["so", "such"],
        "Answer": "so",
        "Difficulty_Level": "2",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128036"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "___________ I saw her yesterday, she was on her way home.",
        "Options": ["When", "Whenever"],
        "Answer": "When",
        "Difficulty_Level": "2",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128037"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "It ___________ a nation of millions to hold us back.",
        "Options": ["makes", "takes"],
        "Answer": "takes",
        "Difficulty_Level": "2",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128038"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "There are only fifteen questions ___________ in this test.",
        "Options": ["go", "going", "to go"],
        "Answer": "to go",
        "Difficulty_Level": "2",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128039"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "The company ___________ accountant was arrested last week has gone bankrupt.",
        "Options": ["which", "whose"],
        "Answer": "whose",
        "Difficulty_Level": "3",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128040"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "I saw her just ___________ day.",
        "Options": ["another", "other", "the other"],
        "Answer": "the other",
        "Difficulty_Level": "3",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128041"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "This is the town ___________ I was born in.",
        "Options": ["where", "when", "which"],
        "Answer": "which",
        "Difficulty_Level": "3",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128042"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "I'm not used to ___________ that.",
        "Options": ["do", "doing"],
        "Answer": "doing",
        "Difficulty_Level": "3",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128043"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": " ___________ your help, I would never have managed.",
        "Options": ["But for", "Not", "Unless", "Despite"],
        "Answer": "But for",
        "Difficulty_Level": "3",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128044"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "No sooner ___________ got there than they started annoying me.",
        "Options": ["I had", "had I"],
        "Answer": "had I",
        "Difficulty_Level": "3",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128045"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "Only when ___________ left, did we notice what she had done.",
        "Options": ["did she", "she did", "she had", "had she"],
        "Answer": "she had",
        "Difficulty_Level": "3",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128046"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "I'd rather ___________ go if you don't mind.",
        "Options": ["not", "not to"],
        "Answer": "not",
        "Difficulty_Level": "3",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128047"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "It's high time you ___________ that.",
        "Options": ["stop", "to stop", "stopped", "stopping"],
        "Answer": "stopped",
        "Difficulty_Level": "3",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128048"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "The company ___________ chairman was sacked last week has called in the receivers.",
        "Options": ["which", "whose", "whom"],
        "Answer": "whose",
        "Difficulty_Level": "3",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128049"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "I wish I ___________ go there on Friday.",
        "Options": ["could", "should", "would"],
        "Answer": "could",
        "Difficulty_Level": "3",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128050"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "If he ___________, I won't stay.",
        "Options": ["come", "came", "comes", "will come"],
        "Answer": "comes",
        "Difficulty_Level": "3",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128051"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": " I wish they ___________ be quiet; they know how it annoys me.",
        "Options": ["could", "should", "would"],
        "Answer": "would",
        "Difficulty_Level": "3",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128052"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "She took ___________ painting after she retired.",
        "Options": ["down", "from", "up"],
        "Answer": "up",
        "Difficulty_Level": "3",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128053"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "She didn't let them ___________ it.",
        "Options": ["do", "doing", "to do"],
        "Answer": "do",
        "Difficulty_Level": "3",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128054"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "By the time I reached ___________, everyone had left.",
        "Options": ["the party", "to the party"],
        "Answer": "the party",
        "Difficulty_Level": "3",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128055"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "Hurry up- the taxi's ___________ to arrive.",
        "Options": ["about", "on the verge"],
        "Answer": "about",
        "Difficulty_Level": "3",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128056"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "You ___________ be better off taking the train.",
        "Options": ["had", "should", "would"],
        "Answer": "",
        "Difficulty_Level": "3",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128057"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "This is the first time I ___________ to her.",
        "Options": ["spoke", "have spoken"],
        "Answer": "have spoken",
        "Difficulty_Level": "3",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128058"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "The negative of 'noble is ___________",
        "Options": ["innoble", "unnoble", "ignoble", "disnoble"],
        "Answer": "ignoble",
        "Difficulty_Level": "3",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128059"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "The adverb from 'public' is ___________.",
        "Options": ["Publicly", "Publically"],
        "Answer": "Publicly",
        "Difficulty_Level": "3",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128060"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "I doubt ___________ she'll be there.",
        "Options": ["if", "that"],
        "Answer": "that",
        "Difficulty_Level": "3",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128061"
        }
    },
    {
        "question": "How old is he?",
        "Options": ["I'm not sure, but he is getting on a bit now.", " I'm not sure, but he is getting in a bit now."],
        "Answer": "I'm not sure, but he is getting on a bit now.",
        "Difficulty_Level": "3",
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "65a6efb75575e0c485128062"
        }
    }
]


